# Martin Ly

martinly727@gmail.com | 0466828181 | GitHub: https://github.com/MartinL77

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/martin-ly-6020a0223

E-Portfolio: https://martinl77.github.io/

#### **PROFILE**

I am currently studying software engineering at Swinburne University with a passion for programming and technology.

I worked at Movember as an intern full stack developer where I helped develop multiple projects with different technology stacks. I implemented new features and fixed bugs where required during each sprint. These projects include:

- Movember Conversations (<a href="https://conversations.movember.com/en/">https://conversations.movember.com/en/</a>)
- Family Man (https://familyman.movember.com/en-au/)
- Ahead of The Game (<a href="https://aheadofthegame.movember.com/">https://aheadofthegame.movember.com/</a>)

I also regularly participate in personal and University projects that involve JavaScript, HTML, CSS, C++, and C#. I also engage in further studies such as online courses and code camps for frontend development which led me to better understand the concepts behind HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React.

#### **EDUCATION & QUALIFICATIONS**

St Albans Secondary College - Year 12 VCE Graduated with an atar of 80.2

2013 - 2019

- Studied various maths subjects along with physics, and English.

Swinburne University - Bachelor of Engineering (Honours) (Professional)

2019 – Current

- Major in software
- Currently completed 200+ credit points

## **KEY SKILLS**

- Technical: JavaScript, Typescript, React, HTML, CSS, GitHub, AWS DynamoDB, Object oriented programming, C#, C++, Arduino, VHDL, Mat lab, and various Microsoft applications like Word, Excel, and PowerPoint.
- **Personal:** Responsible, problem solving, reliable, working in a team, meeting deadlines, taking initiative, and verbal communication.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Intern full-stack developer | Movember

Jan 2023 to Jan 2024

- · Agile team environment with scrum methodologies.
- Committing pull requests through ithub and also approving them after reviewing code.
- Implementation of Google Analytics and tracking.
- Utilising CMS (sanity) to help manage and publish content.
- Learning to effectively communicate and express ideas in a team environment.
- Enhanced proficiency in web development, with expertise in:
  - Frontend technologies: React, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, NextJS
  - Backend technologies: Implementation of API's, Node.js
  - Database management: AWS DynamoDB

# Pick packer | StarTrack

Apr 2021 to Jul 2021

Handles deliveries and works directly with Myer to ship out their online orders.

- Handling online orders and organising the products.
- Cleaning the warehouse regularly.
- Managing customer complaints.
- Organising a schedule to balance work with Uni life.
- · Regularly maintaining punctuality.
- Conversing with managers and completing their tasks.

## **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**

Languages - English; Vietnamese

# **INTERESTS**

My personal interests include socialising, making new friends, learning new things, technology, and artificial intelligence.

#### **REFERENCES**

Jay Cai | Full-stack developer | Movember

Zero.jaycai@gmail.com

0402578576

Harley Reed | Product delivery lead | Movember

0421270225